{
    "questions" : [
		{
            "question": "Which of this teams has NOT won an NBA Championship?", 
            "correctAnswer":  "Orlando Magic", 
            "answers": ["Orlando Magic", "Boston Celtics", "Houston Rockets", "Dallas Mavericks"]
        },
		{
            "question": "What NBA player was the sillouette for their logo?", 
            "correctAnswer": "Jerry West", 
            "answers": ["Wilt Chamberlain", "Michael Jordan", "Jerry West", "Julius Erving"]
        },
		{
            "question":"What company makes the official NBA basketball?", 
            "correctAnswer": "Spalding", 
            "answers": ["Champion", "Spalding", "Nike", "Franklin Sports"]
        },
		{
            "question": "Which NBA team plays their games in Chicago?", 
            "correctAnswer": "Bulls", 
            "answers": ["Kings", "Bucks", "Bulls", "Pistons"]
        },
		{
            "question": "What basketball shot was seen as insulting to other players in the 1940s and 1950s?", 
            "correctAnswer": "Slam Dunk", 
            "answers" :["Three Point Shot", "Slam Dunk", "Layup", "Free Throw"]
        },
		{
            "question" :"Which NBA player scored 100 points in one game?", 
            "correctAnswer": "Wilt Chamberlain", 
            "answers" :["Michael Jordan", "Kobe Bryant", "Bill Russell", "Wilt Chamberlain"]
        },
		{
            "question" :"What is the maximum amount of games that can be played during the NBA finals?", 
            "correctAnswer": "7", 
            "answers" :["4", "5", "6", "7"]
        },
		{
            "question" :"Which of these teams were originally based in Minnesota before relocating?", 
            "correctAnswer": "Los Angeles Lakers", 
            "answers" :["Los Angeles Lakers", "Washington Wizards", "New York Knicks", "Memphis Grizzlies"]
        },
		{
            "question":"How many teams are in the NBA currently?", 
            "correctAnswer": "30", 
            "answers": ["26", "30", "32", "28"]
        },
		{
            "question" :"What other basketball league did the NBA merge with in 1976?", 
            "correctAnswer": "ABA", 
            "answers": ["NBDL", "ABA", "CBA", "BSN"]
        }
	]
}